Md. Sajid Rayhan

Phone: 01329497106

sajidrayhan875@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sajid-rayhan-a1a953252/

GitHub: https://github.com/rayhan52ve/
Portfolio: https://teligati.com/developers-info/



Resume Summary

Insightful computer science engineer who excels at PHP Framework (Laravel), Javascript, ajax & Bootstrap. Have 8 months of professional work experience in laravel development. Always ready for new challenges in programming and web development sector.

Professional Skills

Core Skills : Laravel, Ajax, Javascript, Bootstrap, JQuery, CSS, Git.

Frameworks: Laravel, Bootstrap.

Database : MySQL

Programming Languages: PHP, Java Script.

Work Experiences

Independent Client Projects

- https://teligati.com/ . I have completed this project independently for a known client. Both designed and developed by myself. I will suggest you to visit this website so that you can sence my test in web design along with development.
- http://bendevibraye.com/ A photography website that I have made for a client.

Techweb BD IT – Intern (Laravel Developer)

January, 2024 - Present

I have successfully completed multiple projects tailored to meet clients' specific requirements. Here are some some live projects links that I have worked on:-

- https://webmetrixbd.com/ .An web application to generate documents.
- https://www.shebaralohealth.com/. A business website for Shebar Alo health.
- https://github.com/rayhan52ve/arma-ecom . Single Vendor E-commerce website to sell products & services.

Glorious IT – Intern (Laravel Developer)

August, 2023 - November, 2023

Completed tasks that were assigned as a team or independently under supervision of a mid level laravel developer. Here are some some live projects links that I have worked on:-

- https://umamarket.com/. This is a multivendor e-commerce website that provides service of hiring 10 types of vehicle to customers as its first fase of development. I was attached to this project from beginning till it handed over to our client.
- Some websites and posh softwares of glorious it the company that I worked for ,I was assigned to some budfix, addition & modification tasks are listed below:-
 - 1. https://www.gloriousit.com/.
 - 2. https://restaurant.gloriousit.xyz/.

Systech Digital Ltd – Trainee (Laravel Developer)

January, 2023 - April, 2023

- Worked as a member of the Developer Team for website called SDL Service App. This was a live project work completed using Laravel Ajax API.
- Experienced in working on Azure DevOps as a part of 4 member team.
- Developed a blog project and portfolio project using laravel & Ajax. Worked in git repository.
- Gathered communication and reporting skill throughout the project.

Education

BSc in Computer Science & Engineering

January 2019 - December 2022 University: Uttara University, Uttara. Result: GPA 2.83 in the scale of 4.00.

References:

REFERENCE 01

Name : Mesbahul Alam

Designation: CEO & Founder. Techweb BD It.

Email: techwebdit@gmail.com

Phone: 01618407883

REFERENCE 02

Name: Md Rayhan Robbani Designation: Software Engineer,

Glorious It.

Email: rayhanrobbani1@gmail.com

Phone: 01742-733163